[
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_01_Periville",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99C_MSQ_01_Periville_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99C_Galahad_B",
		"AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_01",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_11",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_01_Periville_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT4_Chestwear_40",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99C_MSQ_01_Periville_title",
		"Description": "@99C_MSQ_01_Periville_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99C_MSQ_01_Periville_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99C_MSQ_01_Periville_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99C_MSQ_01_Periville_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99C_MSQ_01_Periville_completion_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_02_Karburg",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99C_MSQ_02_Karburg_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99C_Galahad_C",
		"AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_02",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_01",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_02_Karburg_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT4_Footwear_40",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99C_MSQ_02_Karburg_title",
		"Description": "@99C_MSQ_02_Karburg_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99C_MSQ_02_Karburg_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99C_MSQ_02_Karburg_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99C_MSQ_02_Karburg_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99C_MSQ_02_Karburg_completion_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99C_Galahad_D",
		"AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_03",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_02",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT4_Handwear_40",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge_title",
		"Description": "@99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge_completion_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99C_BellaRuby",
		"AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_04",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_03",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT3",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01_title",
		"Description": "@99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01_completion_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99C_Galahad_E",
		"AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_05",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_04",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT4_Headgear_40",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine_title",
		"Description": "@99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine_completion_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99C_Galahad_E",
		"AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_06",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_05",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionFamilyWardLostT5",
		"ItemRewardQty": 3,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic_title",
		"Description": "@99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic_completion_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99C_Morgaine_B",
		"AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_07",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_06",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "HoningStoneT3",
		"ItemRewardQty": 3,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier_title",
		"Description": "@99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier_completion_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99C_Morgaine_C",
		"AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_08",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_07",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT3",
		"ItemRewardQty": 10,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02_title",
		"Description": "@99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02_completion_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_09_Canopus",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99C_MSQ_09_Canopus_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99C_Morgaine_D",
		"AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_09",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_08",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_09_Canopus_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT4_Legwear_40",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99C_MSQ_09_Canopus_title",
		"Description": "@99C_MSQ_09_Canopus_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99C_MSQ_09_Canopus_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99C_MSQ_09_Canopus_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99C_MSQ_09_Canopus_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99C_MSQ_09_Canopus_completion_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99C_Morgaine_D",
		"AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_10",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_09",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT4",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus_title",
		"Description": "@99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus_completion_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_11_Lepus",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99C_MSQ_11_Lepus_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99C_Morgaine_D",
		"AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_11",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_10",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_11_Lepus_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CoatingAeternianT5",
		"ItemRewardQty": 3,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99C_MSQ_11_Lepus_title",
		"Description": "@99C_MSQ_11_Lepus_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99C_MSQ_11_Lepus_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99C_MSQ_11_Lepus_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99C_MSQ_11_Lepus_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99C_MSQ_11_Lepus_completion_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_12_Vector",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99C_MSQ_12_Vector_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99D_Galahad_A",
		"AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_12",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_11",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_12_Vector_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "ringweaversfent4",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99C_MSQ_12_Vector_title",
		"Description": "@99C_MSQ_12_Vector_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99C_MSQ_12_Vector_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99C_MSQ_12_Vector_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99C_MSQ_12_Vector_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99C_MSQ_12_Vector_completion_new_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	}
]